### **Quinn Mongeon**

Prooklyn, New York ■ quinn.mongeon@gmail.com (570) 574-6343

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a technology professional with over 6 years of experience across a range of roles and specialties. From QA to implementation, my priority is delivering a product that is well built, a joy to use, and that helps improve peoples' lives.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Technical Implementation Specialist CipherHealth

March 2020 - Present, New York, NY

- · Implement CipherHealth's suite of products, including automated patient outreach (e.g., appointment reminders and post-discharge monitoring) and nurse rounding tools.
- · Gather requirements from customers and design features with product team to support new use cases.
- $\cdot$  Write and execute test plans to ensure CipherHealth implementations satisfy client needs; lead testing sessions with clients.
- · Create project plans to ensure technical components of implementations are visible to stakeholders and are completed on time.
- Implemented a program to monitor patients who received the COVID-19 vaccine at a complex academic hospital system; stood up the call program and the file integration to update their Electronic Health Record (EHR) in a week to accommodate the client's timeline.
- Implemented appointment reminders for a large hospital system's outpatient clinics; the program sends around 12,000 reminders daily via SMS & voice calls, and uses an custom integration to update appointment statuses in their EHR in real-time based on patient responses.
- Received CipherHealth's "CARE" Award in January 2021; this award is given to 5 people across the company each year who most embody company values. I was recognized for being resourceful in implementing creative solutions for important and complex clients.

## Product Specialist CipherHealth

April 2019 - March 2020, New York, NY

- Provided front-line support for the CipherHealth application by resolving tickets and completing build requests submitted by end users and hospital IT teams; managed approximately 20 tickets per day.
- · Point person for critical networking and interface issues; authored documentation and taught classes on the subject.
- · Troubleshot issues with CipherHealth's platform and wrote bug reports for product team.
- · Lead project to upgrade VPN tunnels for clients with an interface; this entailed establishing around 20 new VPN tunnels, and lead to improved network security.

# Quality Assurance & TS Extra Help - Long Term Care, Inpatient, Care Everywhere Epic October 2

October 2014 - April 2019, Verona, WI

- · Wrote and executed detailed test plans to find issues with Epic's software.
- Designed enhancements and fixes to Epic's system alongside developers, ensuring we fully understood the problem and considered a design's impact on other parts of the system.
- · Lead a group to write test cases to test Epic's calculation of RUG codes (RUG codes indicate the level of care a Skilled Nursing Facility resident receives, and are reported to the government by SNFs for reimbursement). We wrote over 20,000 test cases, which we then loaded into an automated testing framework, saving many hours of future testing.
- · Wrote and documented a library of AutoHotKey scripts to help automate testing; taught classes on the subject.
- · Demoed to clinicians to gather feedback on Epic functionality under development 2-3 times per month.
- Provided at-the-elbow support for doctors and nurses on 10+ inpatient go-lives.
- Supported TriHealth Health Systems' Care Everywhere analyst alongside Epic TS; resolved tickets and met weekly with analyst to answer questions and troubleshoot.

### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy, cum laude

Colgate University • Hamilton, NY • 2014

#### SKILLS

Javascript, Java, Python